This type of neck opening is a button down collar.
This is just like on a regular button down the front oxford shirt that has cuffs, boring old plain shirt that a man would wear with a tie.
The button down collar means that it has buttons on the collar very literally.
This would be for typically, simply obviously it's a man, and he's wearing a tie.
Usually they're going to have the buttons.
That's what that's for.
But for women they're it could be a decoration.
You could wear a tie with it whatever you want to do.
Whatever, whatever you want to draw, just draw.
Make sure again that you show that it's a collar that it's going around the entire neck, not just two little squares coming out from the shoulders.
So we want to draw that, and then go down to wherever the collar's going to end.
And then draw our top button and our button placket.
And then draw your buttons to make it an actual button down collar.